thinkexam.com 2019-09-13

# Privacy Policy – Think Exam

## Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy is designed to govern the manner in which Think Exam uses, maintains, collects and discloses the information collected from users of the [www.thinkexam.com](http://thinkexam.com/) website. This policy is applicable to all the services offered by Think exam.  
By visiting the site or using any of our services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as illustrated in this Privacy Policy. Your use of our site and services and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Information**  
The website may collect your personal identification information from the users. This information can be collected using vivid means, including, but not limited to, your visit to the site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources that we offer on our website. The user may visit the site anonymously. However, the personal identification information is collected from the volunteer set of users. The user is free to neglect the sharing of personal information, except that it may restrict you to avail few of the site related activities.

**Non-personal Identification Information**  
The site may collect your non-personal information (meant for identification), to interact with our website. This will include information like the browser name, the type of device used, and technical information constituting the tools that are used to connect to the site, such as the operating system interface, the internet service provider and other related information.

**Web Browser Cookies**  
Our site may also use “cookies” to enhance the user interface and the web experience. The web browser places cookies on their hard drive to keep the records for future, in order to track and check the information. Each of the user is free to select the browser to avoid the cookies, or to alert when the cookies are being sent. If in case, you restrict the cookies, some parts of the site may not function as instructed.

**Use of Collected Information**  
Think Exam will reserve the right to collect and use the user’s information for the following purposes; 

  * **Personalization of user experience** \- We may use the user information for computational analysis. It will help in improved synthesis to understand the services and resources that are provided on our website.
  * **Site Improvement** \- We continuously work to improve our website and enhance the overall experience. This will amend the site offerings, including the information and the feedbacks we receive from you.
  * **Prioritizing Customer Service** \- The information we will be collecting from you will provide an efficient and smooth channel. This will help in simplified handling of the customer service and the support requests.
  * **Process Transactions** \- We may also use the information that is shared by a user, to facilitate our service for a particular order. However, your information and the credentials will be safe and would not be shared with any third party, except in cases when it is required to input the information for avail the service.
  * **Administering the content, promotion, survey or other features** \- We reserve the right to send you the information that you have agreed to receive about the topics and headers we think are of your interest.
  * **Sharing Periodic Emails** \- The email address is required to process your request, that will be used to send information and updates relating to the order. It may be used to respond to your tickets, inquiries, questions, and other requests. However, if you have subscribed to our mailing list, you will receive emails that would be incorporating the website and company’s news, updates, related service information, etc.

**Information Security**  
We have developed an improved data collection, storage and processing practice. The advanced security measures facilitate protection against the unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction details and the data stored on the website. Furthermore, the sensitive and private data exchange in-between the website and the users is monitored consistently. We have authenticated the SSL certification that offers a secured communication platform. It is encrypted in the form of codes that are protected using digital signatures.

**Sharing Personal Information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information. We may share the generic aggregated demographic information that is not linked to any personal information regarding the visitors and the users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes.

**Amendments to the Privacy Policy**  
Think exam prevails the discretion to update the privacy policy. Whenever we will be updating the policy, the updated date mentioned at the bottom of this page will be revised and shared using an email. The team encourages the users to constantly check this page. It will help you to stay updated about the latest modifications that will be helping to secure the collected personal information. You have acknowledged and agreed to hold the responsibility to review the privacy policy on a regular basis and should be aware about the updates.

**Your consent to the terms**  
You are agreeing to the above-mentioned terms of using this site. If you do not agree to the policy clauses, we would request you to, not to this site. Your consistent use of the site that is following the posting of amendments will be considered your acceptance to those changes.
